bestseoideas.com 2015-12-10

# Privacy Policy

At bestseoideas.com we take our ethical responsibilities and your privacy seriously by recognizing that your privacy is important. We have a strong commitment to providing excellent service to all our customers and visitors of this Web Site, including respecting your concerns about privacy.

This Privacy Policy discloses how we collect personal information, the types of personal information we receive and collect, our use of current and former consumer information, as well as the steps that we take to safeguard your information.

If you use this site you explicitly agree to the terms and conditions of the bestseoideas.com Privacy Policy in effect at the time of your use. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the bestseoideas.com site. We hope that this disclosure will help increase your confidence in our website and enhance your experience on the Internet. Therefore, in compliance with industry standards and regulations enforced typically by federal and state governments, we abide by the following Privacy Policy

 **Server Logs**

As with most other Web sites, bestseoideas.com logs web, database, and other server-software usage and access information. This information may include your Internet protocol (IP) address, which in many cases can be translated to an affiliation (such as your work, school, or Internet service provider), or a geographical location. We only use this information for debugging purposes and for aggregating into anonymous usage and traffic statistics.

 **Cookies**

While browsing bestseoideas.com, a small number of text files referred to as cookies are created on your local file system by your web browser at the request of our servers. These files allow us to personalize the browsing experience for users. You are free to delete them at any time, or configure your browser not to create them. However, we do not guarantee that every feature of bestseoideas.com will function as expected without cookies enabled.

 **Third-Party Advertisers**

bestseoideas.com serves ads provided by a range of third-party advertising networks. The practices of our advertising partners are not directly covered by bestseoideas.com privacy policy. We recommend that you read their policies.

To report copyright violations, ownership issues, offensive images, sexual / pornographic content or other inappropriate images. You need to include urls of post & images for removal request via the Contact Us Page.

Please allow up to 5 business days for your request to be validated and to be processed, make sure you entered the correct e-mail address as our staff will contact you to validate your request.
